Hi.
In this segment we're going to talk a little bit about how to do the basic tip.
Now a tip, can be done with your fingers, or your thumb, and the basic thing is, is that you want to make sure that you tip it with the pad of your fingers.
You don't want to tip it on your nails necessarily.
The easiest tips to do are with your pads, the soft part of your fingertips and that way it won't hurt.
Also, another way that I do tips is kind of with my thumb.
I hold it this way.
So basically you want to put enough spin on it, either by yourself or with a throw.
And a throw or spin would come in and you want to strike the Frisbee right in the middle.
Right in the middle with the, with the fatty part of the tip of your finger.
So that's a single tip, you can actually go right and left.
You can actually do multiples, little tips to a big tip.
And what I like to do is actually, tip with my thumb.
So those are some of the different ways that you can do the basic tip.